[{"question": "Choose correct statement about Functions in C Language.", "option1": "A) A Function is a group of c statements which can be reused any number of times.", "option2": "B) Every Function has a return type.", "option3": "C) Every Function may no may not return a value.", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose a correct statement about C Language\u00a0Functions.", "option1": "A) A function name can not be same as a predefined C Keyword.", "option2": "B) A function name can start with an Underscore( _ ) or A to Z or a to z.", "option3": "C) Default return type of any function is an Integer.", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose a correct statement about C Function.?\nmain()\n{\n    printf(\"Hello\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) \"main\" is the name of default must and should Function.", "option2": "B) main() is same as int main()", "option3": "C) By default, return 0 is added as the last statement of a function without specific return type.", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "A function which calls itself is called a ___ function.", "option1": "A) Self Function", "option2": "B) Auto Function", "option3": "C) Recursive Function", "option4": "D) Static Function", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with Functions.?\nint main()\n{\n\n    void show()\n    {\n        printf(\"HIDE\");\n    }\n\n    show();\n    \n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) No output", "option2": "B) HIDE", "option3": "C) Compiler error", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with functions.?\nvoid show();\n\nint main()\n{\n    show();\n    printf(\"ARGENTINA \");\n    return 0;\n}\n\nvoid show()\n{\n    printf(\"AFRICA \");\n}\n", "option1": "A) ARGENTINA AFRICA", "option2": "B) AFRICA ARGENTINA", "option3": "C) ARGENTINA", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with functions.?\nint main()\n{\n    show();\n    printf(\"BANK \");\n    return 0;\n}\n\nvoid show()\n{\n    printf(\"CURRENCY \");\n}\n", "option1": "A) CURRENCY BANK", "option2": "B) BANK CURRENCY", "option3": "C) BANK", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "How many values can a C Function return at a time.?", "option1": "A) Only One Value", "option2": "B) Maximum of two values", "option3": "C) Maximum of three values", "option4": "D) Maximum of 8 values", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the output of a C program with functions.?\nvoid show();\n\nvoid main()\n{\n    show();\n    printf(\"RAINBOW \");\n    \n    return;\n}\n\nvoid show()\n{\n    printf(\"COLOURS \");\n}\n", "option1": "A) RAINBOW COLOURS", "option2": "B) COLOURS RAINBOW", "option3": "C) COLOURS", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nvoid show();\n\nvoid main()\n{\n    printf(\"PISTA \");\n    show();\n}\n\nvoid show()\n{\n    printf(\"CACHEW \");\n    return 10;\n}\n", "option1": "A) PISTA CACHEW", "option2": "B) CASHEW PISTA", "option3": "C) PISTA CASHEW with compiler warning", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with functions.?\nint show();\n\nvoid main()\n{\n    int a;\n    printf(\"PISTA COUNT=\");\n    a=show();\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n}\n\nint show()\n{\n    return 10;\n}\n", "option1": "A) PISTA COUNT=", "option2": "B) PISTA COUNT=0", "option3": "C) PISTA COUNT=10", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with functions.?\nvoid main()\n{\n    int a;\n    printf(\"TIGER COUNT=\");\n    a=show();\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n}\n\nint show()\n{\n    return 15;\n    return 35;\n}\n", "option1": "A) TIGER COUNT=15", "option2": "B) TIGER COUNT=35", "option3": "C) TIGER COUNT=0", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " What are types of Functions in C Language.?", "option1": "A) Library Functions", "option2": "B) User Defined Functions", "option3": "C) Both Library and User Defined", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C program with functions.?\nint show();\n\nvoid main()\n{\n    int a;\n    a=show();\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n}\n\nint show()\n{\n    return 15.5;\n    return 35;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 15.5", "option2": "B) 15", "option3": "C) 0", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint myshow(int);\n\nvoid main()\n{\n   myshow(5);\n   myshow(10);\n}\n\nint myshow(int b)\n{\n    printf(\"Received %d, \", b);\n}\n", "option1": "A) Received 5, Received 10,", "option2": "B) Received 10, Received 5,", "option3": "C) Received 0, Received 0,", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with functions and pointers.?\nint myshow(int);\n\nvoid main()\n{\n   int a=10;\n   myshow(a);\n   myshow(&a);\n}\n\nint myshow(int b)\n{\n    printf(\"Received %d, \", b);\n}\n", "option1": "A) Received 10, Received 10,", "option2": "B) Received 10, Received RANDOMNumber,", "option3": "C) Received 10, Received RANDOMNumber, with a compiler warning", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with functions and pointers.?\nint myshow(int *);\n\nvoid main()\n{\n   int a=10;\n   myshow(&a);\n}\n\nint myshow(int *k)\n{\n    printf(\"Received %d, \", *k);\n}\n", "option1": "A) Received RANDOMNumber,", "option2": "B) Received 10,", "option3": "C) Received 10,", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with functions and pointers.?\nvoid myshow(int *);\n\nvoid main()\n{\n   int a=10;\n   printf(\"%d \", a);\n   myshow(&a);\n   printf(\"%d\", a);\n   \n}\n\nvoid myshow(int *k)\n{\n   *k=20;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 10 10", "option2": "B) 20 20", "option3": "C) 10 20", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with functions.?\nvoid myshow(int);\n\nvoid main()\n{\n   int a=10;\n   printf(\"%d \", a);\n   myshow(a);\n   printf(\"%d\", a);\n   \n}\n\nvoid myshow(int k)\n{\n   k=20;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 10 10", "option2": "B) 20 20", "option3": "C) 10 20", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " Choose correct statements about C Language Pass By Value.", "option1": "A) Pass By Value copies the variable value in one more memory location.", "option2": "B) Pass By Value does not use Pointers.", "option3": "C) Pass By Value protects your source or original variables from changes in outside functions or called functions.", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}]
